morungexpress.com 2018-05-11

# PRIVACY POLICY - The Morung Express

**_ABOUT US:_**

  * Welcome to the morungexpress.com, the website of The Morung Express, a daily English newspaper based in Nagaland. We care and respect your privacy and consider it an important element and asset of our business and recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information and will keep the information you entrust us safe and secure. We do not collect personal information about you when you visit our website(s) unless you volunteer to provide the information to us. We gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This Information cannot and does not identify you personally. We respect the privacy of the users of this service and is committed to reasonably to protect it in all respect. We update, improve and expand our services. Our policies may change from time to time as per the needs and specification of the company. So, please refer back periodically.

**_INFORMATION   RECEIVED, COLLECTED AND STORED BY THE COMPANY:_**

**_DATA REGISTRATION_** **:**

  * When you register on the web site, application and for the service, we ask for basic contact information such as the users name, age, sex, occupation, address, pin code, contact number, and e –mail address etc. When you register using your other account like face book, twitter, Gmail etc., we shall retrieve information from such account to continue to interact with you and to continue providing the services.

**_USE OF INFORMATION BY THE COMPANY_ :**

  * The information supplied by the user enables us to improve our services and provide you with the most user–friendly experience. The information collected from you is primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the services you are accessing, you could be asked various times for your contact address in some cases/ provision of certain services (s) or utility(ies). We normally collect information  on how you use our website, including details of your domain name and internet protocol address, operating system, browsers ,cookies, time spent on a page content, and the route you took to navigate through pages and also other data from time to time to help  us provide you with improved products and services.
  * The main uses of your personal information are to verify your identity, to help provide and administer our services, to review and improve our services to provide access to certain areas of the website, to personalize your visit to our site. The information is also used to notify visitors about events, changes and other information about this site.
  * With your consent the information may also be used for marketing and for market research purpose, including internal demographic studies, to provide, optimize and personalize our services and send you newsletters and information about our products and services.
  * The information we collect is never shared with other organizations for commercial or other purposes.

**BEWARE** of Posting personal and identifiable information freely available /  easily accessible  in public domain like any comments, messages, blogs, available on social platforms like face book, twitter etc, which may be  considered sensitive  and thereby attracting unsolicited messages from other third parties  for which the company has no control and  shall not be held responsible for use or  misuse of such information.

**_COOKIES:_**

  * We use cookies on the website but do not link the information we store in the cookies to any identifiable information you submit, we do not set cookies to store your password. You will still use our website even if you reject cookies. We have no control or access over third party cookies and we do not store any cookies and just use the facility of net framework for page output cache. This privacy statement does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
  * Our site may contain links to enable the user to visit other websites of social plug –ins. However, once the user uses/shares in this links, The Morung Express has no control over these links. The user should exercise caution and look at the privacy policy applicable to the website in question.

**_SECURITY:_**

  * We take precaution to keep your personal information secure from unauthorized access and will store your personal information for so long as it is necessary to provide you our services. You are solely responsible for keeping your User ID and Password Secure. Your password is the key to your account, You shall be solely responsible for all actions taken under your user name and you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding action taken on your behalf. Never disclose your User ID or Password to anyone. If your password is compromised for any reasons, you should immediately change your password.

**_UPDATES/CHANGES IN THE PRIVACY POLICY:_**

  * The internet is an evolving medium, we may change and alter our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary changes in technology, We reserve the right to change the terms and of this privacy policy or the terms of the use. Any such changes shall be notified immediately by posting the new policy on the APPLICATION. Your use of the application or services after such notice shall be deemed acceptance of such changes. Users are advised to review the privacy policy periodically.

**_NOTE :_**

  * This policy does not apply to unauthorized third party advertisements which appear on our website and suggest you to review the policy of such advertisers. Please beware, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. No method of transmission over the internet or the method of electronic storage is 100% safe or secure. Therefore, use the Social media and other platforms wisely with due regard to user’s own privacy and personal details.

**_CONTACT US:_**

  * Thank you for using morungexpress.com, by using this site/app, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. For any complaints, grievances, questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at morung.ad@gmail.com or our head office at Dimapur.
